KIANOOSH SOLEIMANI

REACT JS AND NEXT JS DEVELOPER

Personal information

**** 09395043237

mazyar.solo@gmail.com

Shiraz - Zand st.

Linkedin:

kianoosh-soleimanib5a925225

Skills

React js

Next js

Javascript

Typescript

MUI

HTML

CSS 3

Bootstrap

**

Sass

REST API

Git

Github

CI/CD

Jira 💠🏠🏠

Azure CDN AZA

Cloudinary

Redux PWA

Three is

Node js

Express

Postman

Mongo DB ☆☆☆

Mongoose ★★★

PROFILE

React js Front-end developer with 2+ years of experience in developing projects like CRM, CMS, Blogging sites, Online stores, etc

Self-learner, Teamwork person, Discipline and Punctuality in work, love new challenges, calm under pressure, and following the Cutting-edge technologies to improve me.

EXPERIENCE

Front-end developer, Novin dev, Iran — Apr 2022 - Present

Crypto currency related projects

The current working progress is based on Crypto exchange and money transactions inside the Mother company.

We use techs like **Lerna**, **Typescript**, **Websocket**, **MUI**, **React-Query** (Query), **Web3**, and ext for developing an **Orderbook** that people can put their bid or ask requests in different Crypto and Financial markets.

The learning curve of this process was so useful and interesting for me because we tried to follow the <u>leading techs and Best-practices</u> that made our vision brighter on what we can build with our knowledge.

From the core of this process, we release an Open-source project called **Formalite** and use it in our projects.

Plink of our Open-source project: https://formalite.novin.dev/

Front-end developer, Hillz company, Canada — 2021 - Apr 2022 Admin panel

This project is a **React-based** admin panel for the management of a car dealership that contains parts like managing vehicles data, handling the finances around negotiating vehicles, **customer relationship management** (CRM), controlling their site and blogs, Multilayer structure for gaining level of a simple customer to buyer, **Role base login** with using a **Token authorization** that user can change their roles base on requirement.

Iink of this project: https://www.hillzusers.com/

Front-end developer, Hillz company, Canada — 2021 - Apr 2022

Hillz website

Hillz website is a Static Site Generation (SSG) website using the **Next js framework** that contains information about their company, forms, packages that they offer to customers(Dealerships), and a blog section for SEO purposes.

Personal information

**** 09395043237

mazyar.solo@gmail.com

Shiraz - Zand st.

Linkedin:

kianoosh-soleimanib5a925225

Skills

React is Next is Javascript MUI *** HTML *** CSS 3 *** Bootstrap Sass **REST API** *** Git *** Github *** CI/CD ** *** Jira Azure CDN Cloudinary \(\frac{1}{2} \fra Redux **PWA** Three js Node js **Express**

Postman

Mongo DB ☆☆☆ Mongoose ☆☆☆ I gained the experience of operating and deploying SSG websites in this project.

Front-end developer, Hillz company, Canada — 2021 - Apr 2022

Hillz dealership website

This project is a Server-Side Rendering (SSR) website using the **Next js** framework.

In this project, we try to use the ability of SSR in Next js for creating dynamic sections based on what the dealership wants to show to people and their customers. Dynamic parts of this project come from our back-end that uses Node js and Express framework for the back-end server and MySQL for the database. With this config, we can use this project as a Template for other dealerships that like this design for their website and do not require massive changes in the front-end, just creating a table in the database for them and putting their information in that.

Front-end developer, freelancer, Iran, shiraz — 2021

Bonte takeaway website

Bonte takeaway is a Caffe in shiraz that 5 of my friends established. I tried to help them share their menu with customers in an easy way.

This website is generated with **React js framework** and the challenging part of this project was handling the menu images to get from a **CDN (Cloudinary)** and display it on their site.

This was a good experience for me because I learned how CDNs works and how we can use them in our projects

EDUCATION

Shiraz University of Technology Degree: Bachelor's degree

Field Of Study: Electrical, Electronics and Communications Engineering

2018-2022

POSITION

Lead Front-end Developer at Chadco company in Shiraz.

Front-end Developer at Novin.dev company in Shiraz. (current position)